{
    "subject": "resource/WLGZ-FM",
    "predicate": "ontology/city",
    "object": "resource/Webster,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "WLGZ-FM is located in Webster, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9299134612083435,
            "question": "Where is WLGZ-FM located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6883143186569214,
            "question": "What state is Webster, New York in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6775679588317871,
            "question": "Are there other radio stations in Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6532106399536133,
            "question": "Is WLGZ-FM a radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6066214442253113,
            "question": "Who owns WLGZ-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5921788811683655,
            "question": "What is the format of WLGZ-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5285524129867554,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4361138939857483,
            "question": "Does WLGZ-FM have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3523596525192261,
            "question": "What is the population of Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3498240113258362,
            "question": "What type of content does WLGZ-FM likely broadcast?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WLGZ-FM is located in Webster, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6237_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Webster, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6237_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WLGZ-FM have a website?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6237_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Webster, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6237_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6237_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple \"WLGZ-FM is located in Webster, New York\" as it mentions multiple times that WLGZ-FM (also known as Legends 102.7) is a radio station licensed to Webster, New York, and serving the Rochester metropolitan area."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that WLGZ-FM is a radio station licensed to Webster, New York. This supports the statement that WLGZ-FM is located in Webster, New York."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}